[ {
  "name" : "Default",
  "deckOptions" : {
    "newCardsPerDay" : 10,
    "maxCardsPerDay" : 100,
    "learningSteps" : [ 1, 5, 60 ],
    "reviewOrder" : 0,
    "passMultiplier" : 2.5,
    "failMultiplier" : 0.2,
    "maximumInterval" : 10000
  },
  "cardList" : {
    "cards" : [ {
      "cardType" : {
        "name" : "Default",
        "fields" : [ {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        }, {
          "name" : "Back",
          "content" : ""
        } ],
        "sortField" : {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        },
        "css" : "body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }",
        "htmlBodyFront" : "{{Front}}",
        "htmlBodyBack" : "{{Back}}",
        "totalFieldCount" : 2,
        "htmlFront" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Front}}</body></html>",
        "htmlBack" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Back}}</body></html>"
      },
      "fields" : [ {
        "name" : "Front",
        "content" : "This is the front"
      }, {
        "name" : "Back",
        "content" : "This is the back"
      } ],
      "created" : 1682966492034,
      "interval" : 86400000,
      "due" : 1682966492034,
      "cardId" : 0,
      "learningPhase" : -1
    }, {
      "cardType" : {
        "name" : "Default",
        "fields" : [ {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        }, {
          "name" : "Back",
          "content" : ""
        } ],
        "sortField" : {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        },
        "css" : "body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }",
        "htmlBodyFront" : "{{Front}}",
        "htmlBodyBack" : "{{Back}}",
        "totalFieldCount" : 2,
        "htmlFront" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Front}}</body></html>",
        "htmlBack" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Back}}</body></html>"
      },
      "fields" : [ {
        "name" : "Front",
        "content" : "hejsan"
      }, {
        "name" : "Back",
        "content" : ""
      } ],
      "created" : 1683040168946,
      "interval" : 86400000,
      "due" : 1683040168946,
      "cardId" : 1,
      "learningPhase" : -1
    } ],
    "newCards" : [ {
      "cardType" : {
        "name" : "Default",
        "fields" : [ {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        }, {
          "name" : "Back",
          "content" : ""
        } ],
        "sortField" : {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        },
        "css" : "body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }",
        "htmlBodyFront" : "{{Front}}",
        "htmlBodyBack" : "{{Back}}",
        "totalFieldCount" : 2,
        "htmlFront" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Front}}</body></html>",
        "htmlBack" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Back}}</body></html>"
      },
      "fields" : [ {
        "name" : "Front",
        "content" : "This is the front"
      }, {
        "name" : "Back",
        "content" : "This is the back"
      } ],
      "created" : 1682966492034,
      "interval" : 86400000,
      "due" : 1682966492034,
      "cardId" : 0,
      "learningPhase" : -1
    }, {
      "cardType" : {
        "name" : "Default",
        "fields" : [ {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        }, {
          "name" : "Back",
          "content" : ""
        } ],
        "sortField" : {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        },
        "css" : "body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }",
        "htmlBodyFront" : "{{Front}}",
        "htmlBodyBack" : "{{Back}}",
        "totalFieldCount" : 2,
        "htmlFront" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Front}}</body></html>",
        "htmlBack" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Back}}</body></html>"
      },
      "fields" : [ {
        "name" : "Front",
        "content" : "hejsan"
      }, {
        "name" : "Back",
        "content" : ""
      } ],
      "created" : 1683040168946,
      "interval" : 86400000,
      "due" : 1683040168946,
      "cardId" : 1,
      "learningPhase" : -1
    } ],
    "graduatedCards" : [ ],
    "dueCards" : [ {
      "cardType" : {
        "name" : "Default",
        "fields" : [ {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        }, {
          "name" : "Back",
          "content" : ""
        } ],
        "sortField" : {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        },
        "css" : "body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }",
        "htmlBodyFront" : "{{Front}}",
        "htmlBodyBack" : "{{Back}}",
        "totalFieldCount" : 2,
        "htmlFront" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Front}}</body></html>",
        "htmlBack" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Back}}</body></html>"
      },
      "fields" : [ {
        "name" : "Front",
        "content" : "This is the front"
      }, {
        "name" : "Back",
        "content" : "This is the back"
      } ],
      "created" : 1682966492034,
      "interval" : 86400000,
      "due" : 1682966492034,
      "cardId" : 0,
      "learningPhase" : -1
    }, {
      "cardType" : {
        "name" : "Default",
        "fields" : [ {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        }, {
          "name" : "Back",
          "content" : ""
        } ],
        "sortField" : {
          "name" : "Front",
          "content" : ""
        },
        "css" : "body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }",
        "htmlBodyFront" : "{{Front}}",
        "htmlBodyBack" : "{{Back}}",
        "totalFieldCount" : 2,
        "htmlFront" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Front}}</body></html>",
        "htmlBack" : "<!DOCTYPE html><html><head><meta charset=\"UTF-8\"><title>Card</title><style>body { background-color: #000000; color: #ffffff;font-size: 40px; font-family: Arial;text-align: center; }</style></head><body>{{Back}}</body></html>"
      },
      "fields" : [ {
        "name" : "Front",
        "content" : "hejsan"
      }, {
        "name" : "Back",
        "content" : ""
      } ],
      "created" : 1683040168946,
      "interval" : 86400000,
      "due" : 1683040168946,
      "cardId" : 1,
      "learningPhase" : -1
    } ],
    "learningCards" : [ ],
    "readyCards" : [ ],
    "cardCount" : 2,
    "dueCardsCount" : 2
  }
}, {
  "name" : "Hiragana",
  "deckOptions" : {
    "newCardsPerDay" : 10,
    "maxCardsPerDay" : 100,
    "learningSteps" : [ 1, 5, 60 ],
    "reviewOrder" : 0,
    "passMultiplier" : 2.5,
    "failMultiplier" : 0.2,
    "maximumInterval" : 10000
  },
  "cardList" : {
    "cards" : [ ],
    "newCards" : [ ],
    "graduatedCards" : [ ],
    "dueCards" : [ ],
    "learningCards" : [ ],
    "readyCards" : [ ],
    "cardCount" : 0,
    "dueCardsCount" : 0
  }
} ]